<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The better version of you on prasanth</title>
    <link>/self/self-improve/</link>
    <description>Recent content in The better version of you on prasanth</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 06:00:00 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/self/self-improve/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The elephant in the kiwi burrow</title>
      <link>/self/self-improve/elephant_kiwi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 06:00:00 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/self/self-improve/elephant_kiwi/</guid>
      <description>This is a short blog that I wrote for my then employer; the journey and the writeup was possible because of the kindness of many people - the words more so by Jono&amp;rsquo;s
 It has been a little over two years since I came over to New Zealand from India (the finest country in the world in spite of its chaos, heat and noise, or, on second thoughts, precisely because of that – NZ comes a close second, of course!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I am the best! - Ali</title>
      <link>/self/self-improve/the-finger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 16:00:00 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/self/self-improve/the-finger/</guid>
      <description>In a world defined by cut throat competition, with no one really looking out for you; How do you shine with the skills that you have?
 Here&amp;rsquo;s to the crazy ones.
The misfits. The rebels. The troublemakers.
The round pegs in the square holes.
The ones who see things differently.
They&amp;rsquo;re not fond of rules. And they have no respect for the status quo.
You can quote them, disagree with them, glorify or vilify them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Most Important Blog Post I read this year</title>
      <link>/self/self-improve/build-skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2020 16:00:00 +1200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/self/self-improve/build-skills/</guid>
      <description>Copied over for posterity from: https://neilkakkar.com/powerful-life-skills.html
10 Powerful Life Skills for the New Decade Jan 2, 2021 • Life
Over the past few years, I’ve noticed certain skills in people I admire, from Paul Graham, Vitalik Buterin, to Ender Wiggin.
These are rare skills, responsible for making them who they are. Most normal people, including me, don’t realise it. This makes the skills powerful - not everyone can see them, and very few people have mastered them.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
