<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Literature on prasanth</title>
    <link>/self/lit/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Literature on prasanth</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 06:00:00 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/self/lit/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>OCD</title>
      <link>/self/lit/poem-ocd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 06:00:00 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/self/lit/poem-ocd/</guid>
      <description>OCD Neil Hilborn
The first time I saw her&amp;hellip; Everything in my head went quiet. All the tics, all the constantly refreshing images just disappeared. When you have Obsessive Compulsive Disorder, you don’t really get quiet moments. Even in bed, I’m thinking: Did I lock the doors? Yes. Did I wash my hands? Yes. Did I lock the doors? Yes. Did I wash my hands? Yes. But when I saw her, the only thing I could think about was the hairpin curve of her lips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OCD</title>
      <link>/self/lit/poem-ulysses/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 06:00:00 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/self/lit/poem-ulysses/</guid>
      <description>Ulysses Alfred Lord Tennyson
It little profits that an idle king, By this still hearth, among these barren crags, Matched with an aged wife, I mete and dole Unequal laws unto a savage race, That hoard, and sleep, and feed, and know not me. I cannot rest from travel; I will drink Life to the lees. All times I have enjoyed Greatly, have suffered greatly, both with those That loved me, and alone; on shore, and when Through scudding drifts the rainy Hyades Vext the dim sea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>See It Through</title>
      <link>/self/lit/poem-see_it_through/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 06:00:00 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/self/lit/poem-see_it_through/</guid>
      <description>See It Through Edgar Albert Guest
When you’re up against a trouble,
Meet it squarely, face to face;
Lift your chin and set your shoulders,
Plant your feet and take a brace.
When it’s vain to try to dodge it,
Do the best that you can do;
You may fail, but you may conquer,
See it through!
Black may be the clouds about you
And your future may seem grim,</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Si tú me olvidas</title>
      <link>/self/lit/poem/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 06:00:00 +0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/self/lit/poem/</guid>
      <description>Si tú me olvidas (Spanish) Neruda, Pablo Quiero que sepas una cosa.
Tú sabes cómo es esto: si miro la luna de cristal, la rama roja del lento otoño en mi ventana, si toco junto al fuego la impalpable ceniza o el arrugado cuerpo de la leña, todo me lleva a ti, como si todo lo que existe, aromas, luz, metales, fueran pequeños barcos que navegan hacia las islas tuyas que me aguardan.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
